Right, that's all for today's class.
Remember, college entrance exams are next year,
so studying will eat up most of your summer break.
I encourage you to go out and enjoy the pool or beach while you still can.
In fact, I'd be happy to come with you.
What?
Why the hell would we invite a teacher to tag along?
Don't be dense, Ishikawa.
If there are swimsuits involved, you're going to need adult supervision.
Oh, yeah, that makes sense.
Their stupidity is baffling.
Yasuda would be a certified hottie if he didn't talk.
Maybe, but at least he's a good teacher.
Just ignore the dumb things he says.
Ori, did something happen between the two of you?
This morning.
Hey, Ori. Keep your chin up.
Okay. Random.
Not random if you knew how much I love flat-chested girls.
Flat-chested girls are A-OK.
He thought that would cheer me up.
Wow. Just what goes on in his head.
Oh, yeah. So, Ori.
Hmm?
This guy from another school was asking me for your phone number the other day.
Can I give it to him?
He didn't have the guts to ask me himself, so thanks.
But no thanks.
Oh, what? Again?
Yo. Who's up for some bad singing?
Like today?
Since these coupons expire today, yeah.
Half of two hours? What a steal!
You want to go? Come on.
It'll be fun.
Uh, I think I'm gonna pass.
Ori, you always pass.
I know. I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Huh?
Here you go.
You dropped this.
Thanks. I didn't notice.
He sounded so depressed.
Then again, that's kind of his thing.
I bet he's a total otaku.
This angle's death, my favorite.
Like, into Moe?
A hundred percent.
He has to be.
Does your nerd alert pick up anything?
Hmm.
That dude is one giant mystery to me.
I don't even know if Miyamura has friends.
Sorry!
Gotta run!
And there she goes.
It feels like she hurries home every day.
Must be a boyfriend or something.
You serious?
Well, she's way popular.
It's not that surprising.
You're right!
Hey, Mom.
Got it.
I'll handle dinner.
Overtime sucks, I know.
Bye.
I should probably get going.
Sota!
Hey, Sissy!
We've been waiting for you.
I know!
Let's hit up that store we saw in that magazine over here.
Wait, right now?
Why not?
Yeah, why not?
I'm thinking hamburgers for dinner.
Yummy!
Goo-B!
Yay!
Bye.
Adjust it
Empty
Thank you!
Overtime and working on her day off.
I swear, she's too nice for her own good.
I wish she'd learn how to say no to people.
Sufi?
Yeah?
Are you okay?
Sota!
What happened to your little nose?
I fell down.
Where's your handkerchief, buddy?
So, uh...
Huh?
I'm gonna go since you've got it taken care of.
I didn't even see him there!
Ah, sorry.
Hope he didn't cause you too much trouble.
That's fine.
Anyway, I'll see you later.
Sota?
Uh, you good?
You know, if you're not in any sort of hurry, you're more than welcome to stay for a while.
Oh, I don't know. You sure?
This will be my way of saying thanks. So yeah.
He fell down because this dog spooked him.
I appreciate you helping him out.
And I appreciate you for treating me.
Um, hey bro, why do you drink coffee if it tastes so gross?
I ask myself the same thing.
Your brother's a good kid.
He introduced himself in everything.
Thanks. That's nice of you to say.
He's a real handful most of the time.
Although, taking care of him and all the housework is what's really impressive.
Never would have guessed, Hori.
Yeah.
What's wrong? I mean, you are Hori, right? From class one?
Well, I mean, I am. But how'd you know that?
Do you go to the same school as me?
What? Are you being serious right now?
I'm Miyamura and we're in the same class.
Wait.
What?
That can't be the same person.
If they are, the world doesn't make sense anymore.
You're making one of the weirdest faces in the history of weird faces.
What's up?
Nothing's up.
Are you sure?
Where are you going?
Hori!
Miyamura, got a sec?
What?
You're asking me to come over to your house again?
I'm not asking for me. I'm asking for my little brother, Sota.
He wants that cool dude that saved him from the dog to come play a while.
Really? Then I'll pick up a picture book for him or something.
It's fine. Just showing up will be enough, trust me.
What a relief. Now I don't have to break Sota's heart.
I'm kinda shocked.
By what?
By the fact that you sought me out and are talking to me.
After yesterday and all.
Well, you know.
I thought for sure you'd avoid me.
You really think I'd react that way?
I'm not gonna lie and say it wasn't awkward, because we both know it was.
It freaked me out to see such a different side of you.
But I'm different out of school too, so that'd be a pretty silly reason to straight up avoid you.
Why are you blushing?
I'm just not used to hearing stuff like this.
It feels kinda strange is all.
Still, thank you.
What's with the look?
I just noticed how nice your smile is.
Huh?
You should wear your hair up more often.
Maybe lose the glasses too.
Don't you think?
But then they'd see all the piercings that I have.
You do have quite a few.
So what's the grand total?
It's up to nine.
Four on each year along with the one on my lip.
That is way too many.
My mom would agree with you.
Here are some things I've learned about Miyamura since he started coming over.
I like manga, but I'm not into that moe nonsense.
He is not an otaku.
Brought some cake for you guys.
His family runs a cake shop.
Oh yeah.
That little hole hurt like you wouldn't believe.
He pierced himself with a safety pin back in middle school.
Also...
He's not a very good student.
Unbelievable, honey.
You're like a straight-A queen.
I'm really not.
What's incredible is how a quiet guy with glasses isn't smart.
Is that the rule?
It's times like these when I realize my initial impression of him
couldn't have been further from the person he actually is.
Isn't that a supermarket ad you got?
Yeah.
Eggs are on sale tomorrow, so...
Wow.
His bottom eyelashes are really long.
What's wrong?
Oh!
It's just, there's a sale on eggs tomorrow with no purchase limit.
But it says it only lasts till 4 p.m.
I've got this.
Nothing's gonna stand in my way.
Unless there's a committee meeting, but what are the odds?
All committee members, please report to the AZ room.
You're being called for an emergency meeting.
I guess the odds are pretty good.
But I'm not giving up on those eggs.
I refuse!
Where's the fire, Hori?
She's leaving it up to me!
Can't believe I'm running in the seat.
20 minutes to go.
I know a shortcut.
Egg time!
I gotta go!
Huh?
What the heck?
Wait, what's egg time?
Man, I owe you one.
Uh, rabbit housewives everywhere.
I never want to see another sale as long as I live.
Oh yeah, I almost forgot.
I, uh, kinda sorta ran into somebody on my way there.
Kinda sorta?
Who was it?
That Yuki girl you hang out with.
Oh.
And she saw you...
looking like this?
Yeah, pretty sure she didn't recognize me though.
Surprise.
Uh-huh.
It's time to dig in!
Be careful not to spill.
Okay.
Miyamura, I can't explain exactly why,
but I don't want anybody else to see you this way.
Pretty selfish, huh?
Sorry!
What am I saying?
Forget it.
I'll get us some drinks.
Is barley tea okay?
Go ahead and eat.
It's yummy or hot.
You know what?
Um, me too.
I like seeing you outside of school.
Cooking dinner, getting mad and yelling
so everyone within a five-mile radius hears.
I even like the fact that you don't worry
about your appearance at home
and how you could probably suplex a truck.
I get the picture!
All I'm saying is,
I don't want anyone else to see this side of you either.
And no one will if I can help it.
It's nice.
It feels as if these moments are mine and mine alone.
I told you to stop talking ten seconds ago!
Now you're so close, please.
You're the best!
Jeez, how can you spout off about such cringey stuff
with a straight face?
I know his grades suck, but is he an idiot?
You dummy.
You're worse than a dummy.
You're like a dummy king.
King of the dummies.
If she says the word dummy,
she'll say it at least a hundred more times.
Are you joking?
Dummy, dummy, dummy, dummy, dummy, dummy, dummy, dummy, dummy, dummy.
I guess she does.
What's so funny?!
Everyone has a side that they prefer to keep to themselves.
Listen, Hori.
It's not that I don't like the way you are at school.
I just like this plainer and angrier version better.
I think it's a much cuter version of you.
Somehow, the two of us wound up sharing
our secret selves with one another.
Whatever, king dummy.
It's only going to get hotter, isn't it?
Yep.
Wearing this jacket all the time is going to be torture.
Yeah, but it could be worse, you know.
I'm screwed!
Mega screwed!
We're going to be swimming in B.E.
What should I do?!
You should suck it up and swim.
It's better than running a marathon,
especially when it's scorching.
Swimming is way worse.
It means they're going to see everything.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about these!
There's a fine line between being bold and stupid.
Sometimes I'm not sure where you land.
At least swimming wound up being optional, huh?
Yeah, for real.
But if we have to run a marathon like you said,
I'll probably die of heatstroke because of this stupid jacket.
I don't actually think they'll make us do that, though.
Knowing my luck, we will.
Wow.
I never pictured those two spending so much time together.
Understatement of the year.
Yo, Hori!
You mind if I borrow your notes?
Oh, me too, me too!
Fine!
But you guys need to start taking your own.
I know, I know.
Thanks a bunch for this time, though.
She's popular.
Who?
You mean...
Hori?
Of course.
Uh...
Yeah.
I think that tends to happen when you have good grades.
Let's cut to the chase.
The chase?
Um, what chase?
You and Hori are tight these days.
Are you two a thing?
No!
What gave you that idea?
I thought as much.
I mean, you don't exactly have a lot in common.
Yeah.
True.
Very true.
We wouldn't make a good match in the slightest.
Um, we'd be...
Uh, uh, well...
Use your words, dude.
Don't see them together often.
Come on!
Let's get going!
I'm sorry.
Oh...
What?
I get it now.
Bet you have a crush on Hori, huh?
Ah!
Yeah, so what if I do?
Oh!
I thought you were gonna say no!
But!
Huh!
But that explains why you're always glaring at me when I'm talking to her!
Well, now you know!
Good for you!
I'm so sorry, Ishikawa.
I would have been more considerate had I known how much you like Hori!
I'm now to just the whole school!
Ah, my bad!
I guess I didn't realize it's still a secret!
Hey!
What are you two slackers doing?
P.E.'s about to start!
Ah!
We're already gonna be late, so we might as well take our time.
Uh, come to think of it, now that we're getting to know each other, why do you wear your winter
uniform in the summer?
Don't you get hot?
Um, actually...
I get cold?
You're sweating buckets, man.
Look, what I'm about to tell you might sound a little on the strange side.
Keep an open mind if you can.
Hori's the only person who's seen me without a shirt on.
Really?
Why?
So, if I show you, you have to promise you won't tell our teachers...
The last thing I am is a snitch!
It'd be a real pain if they found out, but I feel like I can trust you.
Ta-da!
Are those things real?
You're only a teenager and you've gotten that much ink done?
Yeah.
Short sleeves would present a problem.
The design's pretty sick, though.
Now you know.
Hmm.
Holy shit.
I totally had you pinned for the weird, gloomy otaku type, but you're full of surprises,
aren't you?
Otaku type, no, but everything else describes me to a T.
Now that I'm getting a good look, he's kinda handsome.
His hair still sucks, though.
So, is P.E. in the gym today?
Is this the kind of face what he's attracted to?
That's my head!
No way!
You have a crap ton of piercings, too!
Okay, next.
You're one strange dude, you know that?
Why could ink or pierce if you're just gonna end up hiding it all?
Uh, have you ever done something completely on impulse?
It's not those things.
Your secret's safe with me.
Though, one thing I still want to know is how you and Hori magically became besties overnight.
It wasn't magic.
It actually started a while back.
Although, the vibe I get is she's just being nice to me.
We're only friends, so there's nothing for you to worry about.
Cool.
So, you won't mind if I ask her out?
Come on, man.
You don't need my permission for something like that.
Guess not.
Just felt right.
That ball's in Hori's court.
It's not my place.
You skipped P.E., slacker!
And you had new duty, too!
So guess who got stuck cleaning up your mess?
Please!
I said I'm sorry!
Sorry doesn't cut it!
What do you want from me, then?
You were hanging out with Toru?
Look at you making friends.
Not really.
We were just talking.
Okay, what's with the cold shoulder?
Uh, what cold shoulder?
The one you're giving me as we speak.
I'm actually hot, not cold.
Did I accidentally offend you somehow?
Will you please just get off my back and my shoulders?
Hori.
I need to talk to you.
Privately.
I'll find you after school.
Well, I...
Hold on!
No worries.
I can pick up Sota for you.
You see what he has to say.
It sounds like it might be important.
Huh?
But...
Sissy's home!
If the two of them wind up dating, I'll be a giant third wheel.
Sorry I'm late, Sota.
I'll get dinner started in a little bit.
Okay, sounds good.
Welcome home.
We need to talk.
If she says I have to stop coming over, then that's that.
I spoke with Toru.
Oh.
He told me, you don't think you and I'd make a good match.
What?
Now I know what you really think.
All of this is just me being nice?
That's the kind of vibe you get?
Wait, didn't he tell you something else?
We're talking about you and me right now, not him.
So you said that?
Admit it to my face!
Yeah, I did.
So, you've been thinking this all along?
Every single second of every single day you came here?
No!
It's just...
I'm boring and depressing.
I put the most emo emo kit to shame.
How could I not be bothering you?
Or ruining your rep just by being around you?
You...
You wouldn't fight me here.
But some days I don't understand why.
Uh, Hori, don't cry!
Why?
You idiot!
Why should you have to worry about my reputation?
Don't assume stuff without even asking!
You better not say things like that ever again, dummy!
Sorry.
Really.
I am.
Just thinking about what you said...
Makes me so mad!
Um, let's take a breather.
If you ever stopped coming to my house...
Who would be around to wake me up when I fall asleep watching movies?
Who'd eat your portion of dinner?
Hori...
I'd have a fridge full of leftovers!
Toru?
He asked, but I turned him down.
Really?
But he seems like a genuinely sweet guy.
Um, what?
Did you just call another guy sweet?
Toru might not be the only one with a crush.
Why not ask him out?
No thanks.
I don't think we'd get very far as a couple in the long run.
Wait, what?
least if then.
Wait there.
First time to.
夢を見たんだ月が綺麗な夜に
また明日ねと手を振る君の姿が名残惜しくて
長袖のシャツに見覚えある道
少し寂しそうに見えた
胸が苦しくなるけど暖かい
気づいた冬の朝だ
約束するよ
近くにいるから見えない物事
大事にするよ
言葉にできないんだけどね
暖かい
眩く者だ
どんなに会いない
ちょうどい
大事playing
何autre guest
少し難しい
お 노래をお願いします
Thank you.